Her life. Her story.
TINA is a documentary, music film directed by T.J. Martin.
Tina Turner overcame impossible odds to become one of the first female
Black artists to reach a mainstream international audience.
Her road to superstardom is an undeniable story of triumph over adversity.
It’s the ultimate story of survival – and an inspirational story of our times.
Self, played by Tina Turner.
Self, played by Carl Arrington.
Self (archive footage), played by Ike Turner.
Self, played by Le'June Fletcher.
Self, played by Oprah Winfrey.
Self (archive footage), played by Diana Ross.
Tina is a 2021 documentary film directed by Dan Lindsay and T.
It follows the life and career of musician Tina Turner.
The film marked the final appearance of Turner before her death on May 24, 2023.
A world premiere was held at the Berlin
International Film Festival on March 2, 2021.
It was released in the United States on March 27, 2021, by HBO, and in the
United Kingdom on March 28, 2021, by Altitude Film Distribution.
The film explores themes of music record, strong
woman, buddhism, 1970s, switzerland.